[
  {
    "question": "How are you, Matt?",
    "answer": "I'm good. How are you doing well?",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "What else were you hoping to cover today?",
    "answer": "No, I think it's good. I mean, ABM... is it's something we need to continue advancing? We've done some fun projects... and have always kind of operated under ABM approach but using additional channels... as a priority force.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "When you say we, is this like a company wide thing? Like who are you talking about your ABM strategy with?",
    "answer": "I mean, sales would be, my partner, it, but we're driving it. I mean, they approach it. Health care is unique in that if you're selling enterprise health care, you basically have 2000 ids that you're targeting. And... so I mean, in essence, if you're gonna be an enterprise health care, you have to be doing ABM, but we've spread downstream somewhat into urgent care and in primary care, large, urgent care and primary care.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much of a priority is that, for your team right now?",
    "answer": "I would say it's a bigger priority for me than it probably is everybody else in the company because we think that far out does that makes sense? I would say sales and customer success are really hyper focused on like what can we do right now with what we've got versus what are we going to do to ramp?",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing channels that you're currently using today. I know you mentioned like a few different like tools and like things that you're using. Are you like running paid ads? Like how are you driving traffic to your website right now?",
    "answer": "Paid ads are not turned on really right now primarily because we just folded over websites and have it fully set up in google Adwords. Again, we need, to get back to that but, we were waiting to see kind of where the dust settled. We still get a third site. We've got to fold in this month. Seo has been historically, a Strong driver for us for around some key terms. But I'm expecting we've got to make up some ground visit.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have any familiarity with xyz before I kind of hop into a little bit at?",
    "answer": "I have a little bit. I think I poked that you all maybe a year ago as I was maybe further back than that to be honest with you, but I know a little bit about you, so.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people are typically in a buying committee for a abc?",
    "answer": "Health system would be like 20 primary care group three or four for... you know, urgent care group. You can two three, four. Something like that. There's a lot of stakeholders that point on the health system side of it.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is low spend customer acquisition campaign to mean for you?",
    "answer": "So you're remarketing at that point Retargeting, okay. Yeah.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you using anything like that today?",
    "answer": "We use defendative health care which is hyper focused, in health care that's probably the definitive healthcare database.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you being brought into a lot of customer meetings?",
    "answer": "Yeah. I tend to be there in one way shape or form... so.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is, is, Trevor?",
    "answer": "Did I invite him? I did not invite him? I.",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shooting it over to the Florence one then from now?",
    "answer": "No, I mean, it's all the same. Yeah, if you don't mind getting like an odd like different domain back us on the big deal.",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has he been involved in some of the conversations with like lassa or tech target?",
    "answer": "Yeah, yes.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the average ad spin that you see your customers doing?",
    "answer": "This really depends on like where they're at, you know, as far as like, it ranges so much in terms of like some people like are just starting with the data and like have very minimum ad spends that like they're just like starting with like google Display ads, they're not really doing much there. And then they're like going upwards of like thousands of dollars. So just really depends on where they're at.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are these your loaded contacts or this is like a there my loaded contacts or are they your database that makes sense?",
    "answer": "This would be our database. So this have you don't have to have these people in your CRM, this would be working off of our database.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have specific personas that you sell to that are like the ideal persona?",
    "answer": "Yeah. Well.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are those titles typically?",
    "answer": "(No direct answer provided in the transcript)",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you return seniority level, of, the users related to the accounts or not?",
    "answer": "Tie it back to the location of where they're coming from. No other there's gonna be able to tell you more like accurately than that based on like GDPR regulations, privacy laws. But we can tell you as.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have health care in there? I didn't see healthcare today.",
    "answer": "That was a different, yeah. Okay.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "What exactly are you hoping to get out of today's call?",
    "answer": "I have a few questions that I can walk through. You know, I think just Matt mentioned it. I just initially had requested Zoom info. So talking through maybe just some of the differentiators there, understanding why, you know, I saw the deck why folks have slipped over... and then a couple of just maybe talking through a couple of the features that were on that like on the bottom of the slide two there. Just so just understanding what to what those do and if they are kind of unique to xyz or if they're you know, pretty standard in the market. It's quick rundown of what I'm looking for there.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you used Zoom info in the past?",
    "answer": "I didn't so I came from amwell, I think there are Zoom info customer and we had a team, that would use it. I probably used it through integration in Salesforce, but I didn't actually use, the ui on it at all.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you looking at this as like a, you know, mentioned Matt as a replacement to definitive health care or a compliment?",
    "answer": "Compliment. I think it's, the best way to look at it. I do, I haven't found anybody that is as expansive, in healthcare is definitive, but definitive is kind of short on contact info. So.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you guys scale pricing based on a number of topics?",
    "answer": "No. So you have an unlimited amount of keywords, it's a little bit different which is important, to note versus topics, with. Zoominfo. Topics are limited to the amount of topics, that they provide you. They have like a hand select of what they're able to offer you what xyz of the value. And like our keywords is that because they're customizable, you can track anything that's gonna be very relevant to your business.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have so with a like, do you have recommended keywords based on kind of the success of leveraging those in the past? Or how does the errors at all? Just we plug in whatever we want customized, how?",
    "answer": "Both, you can obviously start with whatever you'd like as far as the keywords that you want. We could also provide some kind of recommendations based on what other customers that like abc are using. That's part of what, our adoption consultant like CSM team would help you with it's.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "I had a couple of questions on the contact info. So I primarily leverage e-mail it seemed like Zoom info head based on the status that you showed had significantly more emails. Is that, do you guys put a focus on phone numbers or can you walk me through that?",
    "answer": "Yeah. Let me reference what I was pulling up for you in the most recent numbers because they are often changing. We actually just published some new documentation on our contact data that I can send as a follow up as far as like how we prioritize emails and phone numbers. I don't think like we have like an active like, hey, we're only going to focus on phone numbers verse emails. It's a kind of rowing number that we have, but let me follow up with some additional details and like where we, where our investments are going if you will.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anything you're looking forward to this weekend?",
    "answer": "No, I mean, I would like to do nothing that would be my goal but just gonna be... probably mowing grass and doing fine.",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is he like definitive that he thinks like Zoom info is like contact data? Is that what he thinks, is better?",
    "answer": "Yeah. That's that's where he's at and, I, us, I got on a call with them earlier today and they were kind of diving into the marketing side of things... just because I told him, you know, I would entertain it and it's... yeah, it's one of those fun things that it's great to, well, they rely on Bombora, and it's only social media and I'm like it's not 100 percent true but, okay.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that something, that Brian is taking into consideration in his value, the intent data part of it?",
    "answer": "Yeah. Why isn't his primary focus? It's marketing's primary focus on, you know, like he's thinking like the way salespeople used to be in that. I'm gonna go get my people. I'm gonna go target and I need to get all the contacts I can get there. And I'm gonna go, and penetrate and I'm like, well, we can do it smarter, you know, like I think you should do that, but I might be able to prioritize like a handful of people you should be reaching out to each day that are like higher in and more likely to respond to, you know... no. I mean, I think he's like that's cool. It's just, you know, he still wants that expand some data set of contacts, so.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like emails and phone numbers? I mean, it's not part of this package. Now, what would be looking to do, is it like more so like who you like head up via e-mail campaigns? Like nurture campaigns, stuff like that?",
    "answer": "Yeah, yeah.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like how quick are you looking to move on this initiative?",
    "answer": "I mean, he's got an Immediate need and I'm in the middle, of taking is into being more proactive and, you know, we're doing some things that are light lift for us. And I want to get more laser focused. The light lift is more broad spectrum, and I would like to be more Targeted. So what we're discussing, is really me pushing... to build out the remainder of the year, how we're gonna go about it. And then, what we're doing next year?",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does that mean that you'd want something like up and running before? Like the halfway point of the year of like June?",
    "answer": "They, they have way point end of June, maybe end of June? Maybe maybe real? Yeah.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Year start in february is what it or january?",
    "answer": "Well, yeah, no, I mean, I pretty much operated on the calendar here instead of this year, but it's just, yeah, I mean, it's like, the challenge I've got is that I've got a team of four and we're pulling a lot of directions. So I'm still doing a lot of reactive stuff and I'm trying to plan the proactive side of things. So we're gonna do something with ABM whether or not I get it done by the end of June or it happens in the end of july or whatever. I'm indifferent to that, because again, I know I was just told I need to build a strategy for the payer market and I'm like focused on the ship that we've got in, right?",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "What else beyond validating those two points as far as the data tests, do you need to see in order to feel confident in xyz?",
    "answer": "No, I think that'd be a good start. I'm sure I'll have questions, as we get into it, but would just like to see what you had planned here.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does this compare with like how you would currently decide where to allocate spend, where to double?",
    "answer": "Yeah. I mean the whole reason I've been researching ABM is really to get more precise in what we're doing and we've done some efforts in it again using iq via and their last product but they're not, they're really Strong at position personas and physician leadership, but there's a lot of people in healthcare than our physicians that make decisions. And so... I've been looking for basically something like this. It, it would absolutely make us more Targeted in our approach.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did we do on that front?",
    "answer": "Still on the end front? I mean, that's a tool that I really have not leveraged before. So, you know, I guess I don't have a full understanding of how that compares in the market. I contact stuff. I would like to just dig into a little bit more, and look at an account or two, and I know that kind of that, you know, just throw a random account out there. It's not what you guys like to do. But, I would just like to understand how I would get in there or anyone on our team would get in there and review an account.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have a sense of where you're leaning?",
    "answer": "I mean, you know, I don't know that it's fair, to them because I haven't like really done a deep dive into theirs but, they limit the scope of like what you can track. I get more with the marketing side of it than you would get with the sales side of it, Brian. But... yeah, they're just differences and nuances. And, I just don't know enough to say like I mean, right now, I just solve more from you than I have from anybody. So you're leader in the clubhouse because I know more... but, you know, we were talking with tech target, you know, a while ago when we were just starting to do research on this. So, I wouldn't need to go back and revisit conversations with them too.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there like a specific timeline in which you're looking to?",
    "answer": "Some, yeah, I, Brian wants to move quick. I want to move quick but, you know, it more directly impacts him and I want to make sure we're making the right decision so that one side is not negatively impacting the other two, three months down the road. So that's my goal.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given budget is top of mind like, as we work towards putting that proposal together, like does it make sense for us to put an incentivized proposal together, for June and moving forward by then?",
    "answer": "I think that's something that, and I can talk about with regard to what that timeline looks like. We probably will just want to sync on it. I would say yes, but again, this has to be a right decision for all parties here. So... and I can sync on that. I mean, I don't know who would want to be on that call but I can make some time this week to just make sure that I'm comfortable with kind of a dive into an account and what those workflows look like and how to manipulate, and create those maps and whatnot.",
    "rating": "Best"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's going on there?",
    "answer": "Not much. How are you?",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "how are you doing?",
    "answer": "All right, super busy, but going on, but I think like, the plane is going to love a lot. It looks like in the coming weeks... I finally realized why I'm so busy. It's because I came back from Pat leave. And instead of like a slow ramp of like building accounts, which kind of happened like it all kind of came on. And then all the accounts turned on it once, you know.",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now, who said that they would do the direct comparison against Zoominfo?",
    "answer": "Yeah.",
    "rating": "Average"
  },
  {
    "question": "Well, they do, they have Zoominfo right now, no?",
    "answer": "You're 1,000 percent, right?",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Instance or human?",
    "answer": "I'm probably in the demo one that's probably why?",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you what?",
    "answer": "Move from one demo instance to the, to the normal?",
    "rating": "Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "Am I on that?",
    "answer": "Yeah... I'm not sure what to see.",
    "rating": "Average"
  }
]